# **Kevin Flynn**

Full-Stack Web Developer (NodeJS / VueJS)

London, UK 07796977257 flynny85@gmail.com www.kubedev.co.uk www.github.com/k-flynn-webdev

#### **INTRO**

A naturally curious problem solver. 10 years of experience in the games industry creating tools and improving workflow for artists and animators has given me a broad experience of day to day challenges and working in teams.

Being self driven and self taught has given me a different perspective and approach which sets me apart from most other developers.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# AddIntel, UK Web Developer

Oct 2019 - Present Frontend Web Developer

# Self Web Developer

July 2018 - Present Learning full-stack development

#### Freelance Technical Animator

Jan 2017 - Jan 2018

Freelance: Animator-Setup-Tools

### 22 Cans, UK Technical Animator

July 2015 - Jan 2017

Mobile titles: Animator-Setup-Tools

### If You Can, UK Technical Animator

May 2013 - March 2015

Mobile titles: Animator-Setup-Tools

## Traveller's Tales, UK Technical Animator

Jun 2008 - Apr 2013 Mobile titles : Animator

## **PROJECTS**

# BS-Bingo <u>Github</u>

A fun online multiplayer bingo game

# **Daytrack**

**Github** 

A day journal app to help keep track of day/weekly/monthly progress

#### **Pomodoro**

**Github** 

A visually pleasing PWA timer app

#### **SKILLS**

- Design / Mockup
- Html / CSS / SCSS / Javascript
- Responsive Design
- Animation (3d)

#### **TECHNOLOGIES**

- NodeJS (ExpressJS / FeathersJs)
- VueJS
- MongoDB / MySQL
- Nginx
- VPS Deploy
- TDD (Jest / Mocha / Chai)
- C# (Unity3D)
- Unity3D
- Python

## **EDUCATION**

# The University of Bolton

2002 - 2006

BA Graphic Design & Illustration